Fernando Enrique Muñoz Frías

+56 9 5719 9318 | ferm.programmer@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/fernandomunozfrias | github.com/Namnoh | fernandomunoz.vercel.app

Summary

Graduated in Computer Engineering from DuocUC, my current knowledge includes HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Next.js, React, Node.js, SvelteKit, NestJs SQL, MongoDB, Python, TypeScript, and VBA. I consider myself versatile and adaptable, able to acquire new skills quickly. Additionally, I value collaborative learning and am always willing to listen and learn from other's experiences.

Tecnichal Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python.

Frameworks: React, Next.Js, Angular, Tailwind, NestJs, SvelteKit, DJango.

Database: SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQLite), NoSQL (MongoDB).

Others: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Node.js, NumPy, Pandas, Git, GCP, Prisma.

Proyects

Web "Señalando Un Futuro".

University Web App Project.

React, Next.Js, TypeScript, Tailwind, NestJs, Prisma, PostgreSQL, Python

• University group project to create a web application focused on learning Chilean Sign Language (LSCh). The project includes session management and a CRUD system, all connected to a PostgreSQL database. An AI model is also integrated for interpreting signs in real time, providing feedback.

Attendance App: "FastTend".

University Mobile App Project.

HTML, SCSS, TypeScript, JavaScript, Angular, MongoDB, Ionic

• University group project to create a mobile application for attendance tracking in the academic area. This app included a database, user accounts, login sessions, CRUD operations for "subjects," and used the camera for student attendance tracking by scanning a QR code previously created by the professor.

Experience

Full Stack Developer.

Caja Los Andes.

Aug. 2024 - Nov. 2024

Dic. 2020 - Feb. 2021

Language: Spanish (Native), English (B2: Intermediate - High).

Santiago, Chile

Santiago, Chile

2024

2022

- Develop high-quality code for the company's frontend system.
- Create and modify backend processes and SQL queries.
- Primary lead on the migration from Angular version 14 to version 18.

Diplomatic Pouch Sector.

MINREL - Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores de Chile.

- Receive and Dispatch Diplomatic Pouches Worldwide.
- · Prepare Pouches.
- Use Pouch Software.

Education

Duoc UC.

Santiago, Chile

Computer Engineering.

Mar. 2021 - Dic. 2024

Saint Orland N°3

Santiago, Chile

Business Administration with a Specialization in Human Resources.

2017 - 2020

Certifications

- TOEIC English Certification B2 (ETS TOEIC).
- Estrategias Liderazgo Personal en Organizaciones

Standard English Certification (KOE).

(Educación Continua - DuocUC).

Programming Fundamentals Certificate (Programming Hub).
SEO and web positioning course (Udemy).